nextbigsound.com 2009-12-04

# Next Big Sound

_Last updated July 2009_

This privacy policy sets out how Next Big Sound uses and protects any information that you give Next Big Sound when you use this website. Next Big Sound is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. Next Big Sound may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from July 1, 2009.

**What We Collect**

We may ask you to enter the following information voluntarily:

  * Contact information including email address and phone number.
  * Demographic information such as postal code, age, gender, preferences and interests.
  * Other information relevant to customer segmentation (profession, musical tastes).
  * Logos, colors and contact information for your company.
  * Login credentials for third-party websites.
  * Billing and shipping information.

**What We Do With The Information We Collect**

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties other than the bands and/or managers, labels, agents of the specific bands you are subscribed to. We may also use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting. We also require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

  * We may use the information to customize the website according to your interests.
  * To improve our products and services.
  * We may periodically send promotional email about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.
  * Internal record keeping

**Security**

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

**Links to External Web Sources**

Our website may contain links to enable you to visit other websites of interest easily. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

**Controlling Your Personal Information**

You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:

  * Whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website you do not need to fill in any information that is not labeled as required.
  * You may contact us directly to delete any/all of your personal information.
  * You can opt to completely delete your account at any time.
